Finding Aid for Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated
Clarke Historical Library
- Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated.
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #331 Special Olympics Winter #7, Various Competitions,2002 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #332 Special Olympics Winter #8, Various Competitions,2002 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #333 Special Olympics Summer #1, Jim Hornak Interview, Opening Ceremonies,2002 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #334 Special Olympics Summer #2, Various Competition,2002 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #335 Special Olympics Summer #3, Various Competition,2002 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #336 Special Olympics Summer #4, Various Competition, Events,2002 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #337 Special Olympics, Torch Run Check at MSU, Alumni Event, CMU vs MSU,undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #340 Office of International Education, Friendship Family,undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #341 Dialogue Days,2004 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #342, Jazz Weekend,2004 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #343 Move in day, New residential halls,2003 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #344 Trustees Meeting,2003 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #345 Hans Fettig, Senior Nutrient,undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #346 CMU Conservation,undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #347 Flu Shots-Health Services,undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #348 Book Buddies,undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #349 Beach Sand Bacteria #1,2003 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #350 Beach Sand Bacteria #2,2003 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #351 Health Professions Building, Classroom tour,undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #352 Health Professions Clinic,undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #353 CHIP Media Wall, CAVE, Sim Man,undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #354 MSF #1,2003 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #355 MSF #2,2003 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #356 MSF #3,2003 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #357 MSF #4,2003 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #358 Charles Weaver, B-roll,undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #359 Charles Weaver, Interview,2003 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #360 English Language Institute (ELI),undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #361 International Club Performances,204 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #362 Capital Campaign Reception/ Dinner,undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #363 Capital Campaign Dinner #2,undated (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #364 Capital Campaign Dinner #3,undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #365 Capital Campaign Brunch/ Reception,undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #366 Capital Campaign B-roll,undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #367 Capital Campaign B-roll #2,undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #368 CMU Steady Cam Video-Various #1 ,undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #369 CMU Steady Cam Video-Various #2,undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #370 CMU Kesseler Interviews #3,undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #371 Cap, Camp, Interview #1,undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #372 Cap, Camp, Interview #2,undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #373 Cap, Camp, Interview #3,undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #374 Cap, Camp, Interview #4,undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #375 Cap, Camp, Interview #5,undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #376 Campus Scenics,Spring 2003 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #377 TP Toss [Toilet Paper Toss],2004 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #378 Posters @ Capitol,2004 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #379 IRS Fraud Busters,undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #380 Various PBS Shots ,undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #381 Capital Campaign wrap, Weaver Feature,undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #382 Health Building Ribbon Cutting,undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #383 Gambling Forum,undated [2004] (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #384 Student Research Expo, CMU Idol, Gambling Forum,2004 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #385 Court in Classroom #1,undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #386 Court in Classroom #2,undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #387 Puchaiski Softball Pitcher,undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #388 Study Abroad Master, Internet 2,undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #390 CHIP Interviews (3),undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #391 CHIP B-roll,undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #392 CHIP Program Master,undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #393 Scholarship Testimonial Master,undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #394 Tribal After-School Program,undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #395 Testing Center,undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #396 B-ball in El. School,undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #397 Orientation Owens parts 1 and 3,undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #398 Orientation Owens part 2,undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #399 Summer Reading Clinic,undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #400 Massasauga Rattler Research #1,undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #401 Massasauga Rattler Research, Brad Swanson Interview #2,undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #402 Carter O Alumni visit,undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #403 Rao-Strider, Homecoming Parade,2004 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #404 Weed research interview #2,undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #405 Airboat-Weed Research #1,undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #406 Brown vs Bd of Ed, Interview with Matthew Perry and Fred Gra,undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #407 Brown vs Bd of Ed, forum #2,undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #408 Music Lab,undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #409 Get Acquainted Day,2004 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #410 Mainstage,2004 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #411 Michael Moore Appearance,undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #412 School House Grant,undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #413 RPL (Recreation, Parks, and Leisure) Gobblefest Poker,undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #414 RPL Climbing Wall,undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #415 Michigan story Fest #1, Garrison Keillor,2004 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #416 Michigan Story Fest #2,2004 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #417 Michigan Story Fest #3,2004 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #418 Garrison Keillor at CMU,2004 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #419 SAC Video #1,undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #82 Graduation,December 2004 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #83 Campus Tour 1998; Academic Advising, Job Fair, 1999,1998; 1999 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #84 Sports Complex Groundbreaking, 1997; CMU and You Day, 1998,1997; 1998 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #85 Student Success Center, 1997; Minority Residential Hall, 2000,1997; 2000 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #86 Student Research Expo,1999 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #87 Broadway Rehearsal,undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #88 Welcome Back Activities,undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #89 Climbing Club,undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #90 Civility Panel,undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #91 1 in 4 #1,undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #92 1 in 4 #2,undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #93 Art Van-CMU Intern, Vlassis Interview and B-roll,undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #94 Bandit Industries, CMU Intern,undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #95 Vlassis, 2 CMU Interns,undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #96 Troy CEL Classes,undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #97 Pat Summit Presser Leadership Interview, Unveiling,undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #98 Library Construction Update, Sandy Pety Kiewice- Alum still, Bret Holey Alum NBC,2001 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #99 CEL Library Services,undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #100 Wx Shots, Library Window reflect PBS Tower,undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #101 Campus Scenics, Library Construction,2000 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #102 Library Construction Tour,2000 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP ##103 No Label,undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP 104 Library Groundbreaking, outside shots prior to construction,1999 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #105 Library, Arches lifted in place,1999 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #106 No Label,undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #107 Various Business Classes,undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #108 Business Classes, SAP (Systems Applications and Products in data processing) Lab, CBA sign, Grawn exteriors,undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #109 Orientation,2001 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #110 Little Shop of Horrors – Play,2001 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #111 No Labelundated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #112 WMHW Takeover,undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Videotapes: BetacamSP #113 E-band,undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Student Media,1985-2000 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Student Organizations,1993-2013 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Students,1997-2012 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Teacher Education Professional Development,1985-2014 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Theatre,1989-2014 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Transportation Studies Center,1994 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Tuition and fees,1977-2012 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: University Park,1987-1992 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: University Relations,1987-1999 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Veterans Resource Center,2012-2013 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Volunteer Center,1994-2014 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Women’s Studies Program,1990-2006 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - News, organized by Subjects, S-W: Wood Chip Plan,2001 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Progress Edition,1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Program Board,2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Provost,1986-2013 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Psychology,1988-2014 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Public Broadcasting,1986-2009 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Public Relations,1990-2008 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Public Safety,1985-2014 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Real Estate Program,2006 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Recreation and Park Administration,1991-2014 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Registration,1986-2012 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Religion,1986-2006 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Residences and Auxiliary Services,1998-2007 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Residential Colleges,1999-2005 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Retirements,1990-2012 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: SAP,1998-2014 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Saginaw Chippewa Indian Tribe,1995-2002 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Scholarships/ Awards,1991-2013 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: School of Banking,1991-2005 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Sculpture,1991 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: School of Public Service and Global Citizenship,2013 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Science and Technology,2000-2005 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Sesquicentennial of Michigan prepared by CMU,1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Sexual Assault Programs,1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Small Business Center,1989-2000 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: SmartZone,2001-2007 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: SASW (Sociology, Anthropology and Social Work),1990-2014 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Soviet Exchange,1987-1991 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Speakers,2012-2014 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Special days/ events,1992-2014 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Special Olympics,1988-2014 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Speech Communication and Dramatic Arts,1989-2008 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Sports Medicine,2000-2003 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: State Literacy Resource Center,1994-1998 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Strategic Planning,1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Staff Personnel,1994-1996 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Student Activity Center,1994-2001 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Student Affairs,1984-2012 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - News, organized by Subject P-S: Student Life,1986-2008 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 201-400,1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 401-600,1980 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 601-800,1980 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 801-1000,1980 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 1001-1200,1980 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 1201-1400,1981 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 1401-1579,1981 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 001-236,1981 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 237-532,1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Information Services News, 1979-1982: Information Services News, 524-751,March-June 1982 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Information Services News, 1982-1984: Information Services News, 761-1036,July-November 1982 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Information Services News, 1982-1984: Information Services News, 1037-207,December 1982-March 1983 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Information Services News, 1982-1984: Information Services News, 208-500,April-September 1983 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Information Services News, 1982-1984: Information Services News, 501-663,September-November 1983 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Information Services News, 1982-1984: Information Services News, 664-850,1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Information Services News, 1982-1984: Information Services News, 851-1200,1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Information Services News, 1982-1984: Information Services News, 1-199,1984 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Information Services News, 1982-1984: Information Services News, 200-399,1984 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Information Services News, 1984-1987: Information Services News, 400-600,1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Information Services News, 1984-1987: Information Services News, 601-824,1985 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Information Services News, 1984-1987: Information Services News, 344-580,1986 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Information Services News, 1984-1987: Information Services News, 581-759,1986 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Information Services News, 1984-1987: Information Services News, 760-939,1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Information Services News, 1984-1987: Information Services News, 940-1167,1987 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Information Services News, 1984-1987: Information Services News, 1171-1357,1987 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Information Services News, 1987-1990: Information Services News, 1359-1608,1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Information Services News, 1987-1990: Information Services News, 1609-1824,1988 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Information Services News, 1987-1990: Information Services News, 1825-2089,1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Information Services News, 1987-1990: Information Services News, 2090-2281,1989 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Information Services News, 1987-1990: Information Services News, 2283-2467,1989 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Information Services News, 1987-1990: Information Services News, 2468-2705,1989 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Information Services News, 1987-1990: Information Services News, 2524-2876,1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Information Services News, 1987-1990: Information Services News, 2877-3056,1990 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Information Services News, 1990-1994: Information Services News, 3057-3200,1990 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Information Services News, 1990-1994: Information Services News, 3201-3404,1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Information Services News, 1990-1994: Information Services News, 3405-3653,1991 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Information Services News, 1990-1994: Information Services News, 3654-3998,1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Information Services News, 1990-1994: Information Services News, 4000-4293,1992 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Information Services News, 1990-1994: Information Services News, 4294-4675,1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Information Services News, 1990-1994: Information Services News, 4677-5008,1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Information Services News, 1994-1997: Information Services News, 5009-5375,1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Information Services News, 1994-1997: Information Services News, 5376-5639,1995 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Information Services News, 1994-1997: Information Services News, 5641-5891,1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Information Services News, 1994-1997: Information Services News, 5892-6038,1996 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Information Services News, 1994-1997: Information Services News, 6039-6102,1996 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Information Services News, 1994-1997: Information Services News, 6103-6319,1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Information Services News, 1994-1997: Information Services News, 6320-6512,1997 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Troutman,undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Trout,undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: University Center (UC),undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Veit’s Woods,undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Warriner,undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Wheele,undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Wightman,undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Woldt,undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: New residence halls (by Woldt),undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Wood Chip Plant,undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Nation’s Bicentennial News Releases,undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Old Library,undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Park Library,undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Park Library Addition,undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Pearce Hall,undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: President’s House,undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Gerald L. Poor Museum (old school house),undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Powers Music Building,undated (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Robinson,undated (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Ronan,undated (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Rose Center,undated (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Rowe,undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Rowe Hall Fire ,undated (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Saxe,undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Sloan,undated (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Smith Hall,undated (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Student Activity Center,undated (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Sweeny,undated (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Tate,undated (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Thorpe,undated (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Towers Additions,undated (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Health Building,undated (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: New IET Building,undated (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Herrig,undated (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Kelly/ Shorts Football Stadium,undated (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Larzelere,undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Library and Information Services Center,undated (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Married Housing,undated (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Merrill,undated (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Moore,undated (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Motor Pool,undated (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Music Building,undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: North Art Studio Art Building (New),undated (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Alumni House Building,undated (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - News Organized by Subject, CMU buildings, A-Z: Alumni Field,undated (Box 48, Folder 45)